smicschool.com 2018-01-22

# SMIC Private School: Privacy Policy

SMIC Private School (SMIC) is committed to protecting any personal information shared on this site. 

Anyone can visit [](http://www.smic-school.cn%28tbd/)[www.smicschool.com](http://www.smic-school.cn/) without revealing any personal information. We do not collect any personal information unless you voluntarily provide it by sending us e-mail, participating in a survey, or completing an on-line form requested by admissions or administrators. Such information will be used by SMIC only to conduct official school business and will never be transferred to any unaffiliated third party.

 **Commitment to Security**

The School is committed to ensuring the safety of the Website and its users. This site has security measures in place to protect all information under our control. Photographs of the SMIC School community members, including students, alumni, faculty, staff, are used on SMIC Private School Website and social media sites, and are not to be shared with non-school sources. We do not post, or permit constituents to post images that might be deemed inappropriate.

We will honor all requests by users who wish to have images of themselves removed from the website or social media sites. To make such a request, please contact [communications@smicschool.](mailto:communications@smicschool.) __com ****.

SMIC respects the privacy of every constituent who accesses our website.

 _[](http://www.smic-school.cn/)_

Please be aware SMIC Private School has no control over materials once they are posted online, and these may be viewable by the general public and can be copied or sent without our knowledge or permission.

 **Copyrighted Materials**

All materials on this site are copyrighted by SMIC Private School unless otherwise indicated. SMIC will not post non-SMIC-owned copyrighted material without written permission from the appropriate parties.

 **Legal Information**

SMIC Private School provides links to other websites or resources. We do not control these sites and resources, do not endorse them, and are not responsible for their availability, content, or delivery of services. In particular, external non-SMIC sites are not bound by SMIC Private School’s privacy policy.

  * School Calendar
  * Faculty & Staff Directory
  * School News
